freshtechweb.com 2014-03-12

# Privacy Policy | Fresh Tech Web

**[Privacy Policy](http://www.freshtechweb.com/users-oblivious-and-the-eu-doubtful-as-google-will-now-save-the-web-searches.html) for [Freshtechweb](http://www.freshtechweb.com/welcome-to-fresh-web-tech.html).com**

If you require any more information about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at freshtechweb@gmail.com.

At Freshtechweb.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by Freshtechweb.com and how it is used.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, Freshtechweb.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes [internet](http://www.freshtechweb.com/important-differences-between-linux-hosting-and-windows-hosting.html) protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
Freshtechweb.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

Hello All, I’m [Andrew Norton](https://plus.google.com/108462944052739299225/?rel=author) a professional blogger and writer. I love to write and share about technology related news. I hope you all will enjoy reading my blog. Thanks!
